[
    {
        "title": "TV"
    },
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "What is the longest-running soap opera on UK television?",
        "answer": "Coronation Street"
    },
    
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "David Tennant, Matt Smith, Peter Capaldi, Jodie Whittaker and Ncuti Gatwa have all starred as the protagonist in which show?",
        "answer": "Doctor Who"
    },
    
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "What is the name of the British period drama series set in the Yorkshire Dales?",
        "answer": "Emmerdale"
    },
    
    
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "Which British TV series follows the lives of the Crawley family and their servants in the early 20th century?",
        "answer": "Downton Abbey"
    },
    
    
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "What is the name of the British TV series that follows the lives of the Shelby crime family in post-World War I Birmingham?",
        "answer": "Peaky Blinders"
    },
    
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "Which British sitcom revolves around the lives of brothers living in the fictional Nelson Mandela House?",
        "answer": "Only Fools and Horses"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "What is the name of the British TV series that follows the lives of several families in the fictional Albert Square?",
        "answer": "EastEnders"
    },
    
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "Which British TV series features a group of amateur bakers competing in a series of rounds?",
        "answer": "The Great British Bake Off (or The Great British Baking Show)"
    },
    
    
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "Which British TV show features a duo of quirky detectives investigating unusual crimes in the fictional town of Summerisle?",
        "answer": "Death in Paradise"
    },
    
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "Which British TV series follows the lives of the residents of a cul-de-sac in suburban Manchester?",
        "answer": "Cold Feet"
    }
]
